Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
- Center for Urban Science and Progress (RG 37.52), July 2017-ongoing
  - Center for Urban Science and Progress Doctoral Track, February-October 2023
    Requirements for the doctorate in Urban Science: Complexity, Informatics, & Sensing at the Center for Urban Science and Progress. Includes descriptions for the complexity, informatics, and sensing courses; the urban science colloquium; the dissertation component; and admission information.
  - Center for Urban Science and Progress Graduate Programs, February 2023-February 2024
    Information on the Center for Urban Science and Progress Master of Science and Online Advanced Certificate programs.
  - Center for Urban Science and Progress Doctoral Track, June-November 2023
  - Center for Urban Science and Progress Doctoral Track Course Descriptions, November 2023-ongoing
    Course descriptions for the urban science doctoral track at the Center for Urban Science and Progress.
  - Center for Urban Science and Progress Graduate Programs, February 2024-ongoing
- Center for Data Science (RG 37.55), July 2014-ongoing
  - Center for Data Science Master of Science in Data Science, July 2014-March 2021
    Website detailing the curriculum and courses for the MS in Data Science. Website redirects to the homepage for the Center for Data Science in 2019.
  - Center for Data Science MS in Data Science Curriculum, September 2016-April 2017
    Curriculum tracks for the MS in Data Science. Includes 4 semester and 3 semester options, required courses, and pre-approved elective courses.
  - Center for Data Science Required Courses, September 2016-April 2017
    Listing of required courses and the order they should be taken in for the MS in Data Science.
  - Center for Data Science Pre-Approved Elective Courses, September 2016-April 2017
    Listing of all electives approved for Data Science graduate students organized by discipline or domain.
  - Center for Data Science PhD in Data Science, April 2017-ongoing
    Overview of the PhD in Data Science, with links to the study areas and faculty, curriculum, admission requirements, an FAQ, the medical school track, and the National Science Foundation Research Traineeship Future program.
  - Center for Data Science MS in Data Science Curriculum, November 2017-March 2021
    Degree requirements for the MS in Data Science. Includes a listing of required courses, pre-approved elective information, course plans, data science track, data science big data track, data science mathematics and data track, data science natural language processing track, data science physics track, data science biology track, and data science biomedical information track. In 2020, the URL redirects to the Center for Data Science homepage.
  - Graduate School of Arts & Science, Master of Science in Data Science, May 2018-ongoing
    This page lists the degree requirements for the Master of Science program at New York University's Center for Data Science, including required core courses and links to information about elective requirements, and information about the Master's capstone project.
  - Center for Data Science Undergraduate Program, October 2019-March 2020
    Overview of the Center for Data Science's undergraduate program. Includes information on the major and minors in data science, course listings, and an FAQ.
  - Center for Data Science PhD in Data Science, October 2019-March 2020
    Overview of the Center for Data Science's PhD in Data Science. Includes details on the curriculum, admission requirements, faculty, and an FAQ. It also includes information on data science areas of concentration, specifically machine learning and perception, science and applications, theory, data management, and healthcare.
  - Center for Data Science MS in Data Science Curriculum, October 2019-March 2020
    This page lists courses offered by the MS Data Science program as well as out of approved out-of-department course offerings, and a sample 4 semester degree map/course plan. The page features links to individual class sites, as well as other pages with information about the NYU Center for Data Science.
  - Center for Data Science MS in Data Science Curriculum, March-June 2020
  - Center for Data Science Undergraduate Courses, March 2020-ongoing
    Undergraduate courses offered at the Center for Data Science, including the Data Science for Everyone, Introduction to Data Science, Causal Inference, Responsible Data Science, and Advanced Topics in Data Science class descriptions.
  - Center for Data Science Undergraduate Program, March 2020-ongoing
    Overview of the undergraduate data science program. Includes information on the major and minor programs, joint major programs, courses offered, remote learning experiences in data science, and an FAQ on the program.
  - Center for Data Science PhD in Data Science Curriculum, March 2020-ongoing
    Curriculum for the PhD in Data Science. It includes the degree requirements, required course descriptions, elective courses, teaching requirement, comprehensive exam, depth qualifying exam, dissertation information, and an example course sequence.
  - Center for Data Science Course Offerings, June 2020-October 2023
    Listing of courses offered at the Center for Data Science. Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the website focuses on hybrid model of in-person and remote teaching for all course offerings.
  - Center for Data Science Fall 2021 Courses, July 2021
  - Center for Data Science Course Offerings, March 2023
    Listing of courses offered at the Center for Data Science for the Spring 2023 semester.
  - Center for Data Science, February 2024
- Tandon School of Engineering (RG 48), 1981-ongoing
  Includes Polytechnic Institute of New York materials.
  - Bulletins, 2009-2011 (Box 171)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 1981-1990, 1992-1995, 1999-2016; cuid17997
  - Polytechnic Undergraduate and Graduate Bulletin (with addenda), May 2014-August 2018
  - Tandon School of Engineering Undergraduate and Graduate Bulletin, April 2015-ongoing
    NYU Tandon (formerly the Polytechnic School of Engineering) bulletins for 2014-2016, 2016-2018, 2018-2020, and 2020-2022. The bulletins includes graduate and undergraduate academic requirements and policies; academic department and degree and program information; lists of academic programs and curricula; and course descriptions. Also includes PDFs of bulletins dating back to 1981.
  - Polytechnic Institute of NYU Undergraduate and Graduate Catalog, April 2017-March 2021
    PDF of the NYU Poly undergraduate and graduate catalog for 2011-2013.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The Tandon bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their certificate, masters, and PhD programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each degree.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The Tandon bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate majors and minors. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each degree.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Applied Urban Science and Informatics, M.S., February 2024-ongoing
    Webpage for the Applied Urban Science and Informatics masters at the Tandon School of Engineering in partnership with the Center for Urban Science and Progress. The website includes a curriculum overview.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Applied Urban Science and Informatics, OAC, February 2024-ongoing
    Webpage for the online advanced certificate for Applied Urban Science and Informatics at the Tandon School of Engineering in partnership with the Center for Urban Science and Progress. The website includes a curriculum overview.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Urban Science: Sensing, Complexity, & Informatics, Doctoral Track, February 2024-ongoing
    Webpage for the Urban Science: Sensing, Complexity, & Informatics doctoral track at the Tandon School of Engineering in partnership with the Center for Urban Science and Progress. The website includes a curriculum overview.
- NYU Abu Dhabi (RG 49), 2015-ongoing
  - Bulletin (PDF), 2015-2016
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Primary and Secondary Educational Engagement, September 2016
    The Office of Primary and Secondary Educational Engagement builds bridges between K-12 and higher education. The webpage contains information on the faculty speakers bureau and the activities and events of the Office.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2015-2016, September 2016
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin for 2015-2016.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Academics, September 2016
    Website featuring information on NYUAD's academic divisions: Arts and Humanities, Engineering, Science, and Social Science.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Undergraduate Courses, September 2016
    Full listing of undergraduate courses offered at NYU Abu Dhabi for Fall 2015 to Spring 2017.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed Scholars Program Course Descriptions, September 2016
    Descriptions for the courses in the program: U.S. Supreme Court's Treatment of the Relationship Between Church and State, US Foreign Policy, What Makes a Great Leader?, Public Speaking & Public Presentations, and Critical Thinking and Persuasive Writing.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Summer Academy Curriculum, September 2016
    Website for NYUAD's summer academy curriculum, which included instruction in Critical Thinking and Writing, Mathematical Reasoning for the Sciences, Standardized Test Preparation, and Leadership Development and Public Speaking.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2016-17, September 2016-November 2017
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin for 2016-2017.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Executive Education, September 2016-ongoing
    The page contains information about NYU Abu Dhabi's executive education program, with an overview page and subpages on Custom Programs and Case Studies.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin, November 2017-August 2018
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi undergraduate bulletin for 2017-2018.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Graduate Global PhD Student Fellowships, November 2017-ongoing
    Website containing information on the PhD fellowship programs offered at NYU Abu Dhabi, including Art and Media, Biology, Chemical Engineering, Chemistry, Civil Engineering, Computer Science, Economics, Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Psychology, Physics, and Transportation Planning and Engineering.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Undergraduate Core Curriculum, April 2019-ongoing
    NYU Abu Dhabi Undergraduate Core Curriculum consists of two Core Colloquia, each of which addresses a significant global challenge from multidisciplinary perspectives, and four Core Competency Courses, one each in the four categories: Arts, Design, and Technology; Cultural Exploration and Analysis; Data and Discovery; and Structures of Thought and Society. Includes a PDF with the course descriptions.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin, February-October 2019
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi undergraduate bulletin for 2018-2019.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2019-2020, October 2019
    PDF of the 2019-2020 course bulletin for NYU Abu Dhabi including a mission statement, academic calendar, core curriculum, and programs at a glance, accreditation, degree requirements, and admissions for the NYUAD campus as well as departmental/program descriptions and individual course listings.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletins, October 2019-June 2020
    Webpage containing pdfs to the current and previous NYU Abu Dhabi bulletins, dating back to 2013.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Core Curriculum User Guide, 2019-2020, October 2019-June 2020
    PDF for NYU Abu Dhabi's core curriculum. It includes the mission statement for NYUAD and a description of the NYUAD Core, which consists of two Core Colloquia, each of which addresses a significant global challenge from multidisciplinary perspectives, and four Core Competency Courses, one each in the four categories: Arts, Design, and Technology; Cultural Explorations and Analysis; Data and Discovery; and Structures of Thought and Society. It also describes other core classes, including the first year writing seminar, quantitative reasoning, experimental inquiry, and Islamic studies.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2020-2021, March 2021
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin for 2020-2021.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2021-2022, October 2021-March 2022
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin for 2021-2022.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Master of Fine Arts in Art and Media, October 2023-ongoing
    This page contains information on the Master of Fine Arts in Art and Media program at NYU Abu Dhabi. It contains course requirements, descriptions, program structure, learning outcomes, and faculty.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Master of Science in Economics, October 2023-ongoing
    This page contains information on the Master of Science in Economics program at NYU Abu Dhabi. It contains course requirements, descriptions, program structure, learning outcomes, and faculty.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The NYU Abu Dhabi bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their masters programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The NYU Abu Dhabi bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each major and minor, as well as the required core curriculum.
- NYU Shanghai (RG 50), 2013-ongoing
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2013-2016; cuid17998
  - NYU Shanghai Academic Bulletin, March 2015-ongoing
    Landing page linking to PDFs of the NYU Shanghai Bulletin. Contains the 2013-2014, 2014-2015, 2015-2016, 2016-2017, 2017-2018, and 2018-2019 bulletins and updates to the bulletins.
  - NYU Shanghai Majors and Minors, March 2015-ongoing
    Listing of all of the majors and minors offered at NYU Shanghai. Each major and minor links to a page describing the degree requirements, courses offered that semester, curriculum worksheets, faculty mentors, concentration options, and minor requirements.
  - NYU Shanghai Graduate and Advanced Education, September 2016-ongoing
    Information on graduate and advanced studies at NYU Shanghai. The webpage focuses on the Master's and PhD programs, research fellowship programs, study away programs in Shanghai, as well as news and events related to convocation. Pages on the Master's program and PhD programs provide explanations of the structures of the programs.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin Updates, May 2017-June 2020
    Updates to the NYU Shanghai bulletins from 2013-2019.
  - NYU Shanghai Core Curriculum, March 2019-ongoing
    This is the core curriculum page for New York University's Shanghai campus, which details general education requirements like Social & Cultural Foundations, Writing, Mathematics, Science, Algorithmic Thinking, and Language requirements. There is also information about specific courses that will fulfill these requirements and a short video by the academic advising office that discusses the NYU Shanghai core curriculum.
  - NYU Shanghai PhD Programs, March 2019-ongoing
    This page details PhD programs offered by NYU Shanghai, with links to pages for the individual programs detailing current supervising faculty, program structure, application information, and profiles of current students. PhD programs include biology, chemistry, computer science, data science, mathematics, neural science, physics, and transportation planning and engineering.
  - NYU Shanghai Master's Programs, March 2019-ongoing
    This page details the Master's programs offered by NYU Shanghai, with links to pages for the individual programs. Master's programs include Data Analytics & Business Computing, Interactive Media Arts, Marketing and Retail Science, Organization Management and Strategy, Quantitative Finance, Social Work, and Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2019-2020, October 2019
    PDF of undergraduate course bulletin for NYU Shanghai, featuring basic campus information, enrollment information, degree requirements, and course listings by degree program.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Quantitative Finance Curriculum, October 2019-June 2020
    Curriculum page for NYU Stern Shanghai's MS program in quantitative finance, including course listings and descriptions, as well as links to other information about this and other degree programs offered by Stern Shanghai.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics & Business Computing Curriculum, October 2019-June 2020
    Curriculum page for NYU Stern Shanghai's MS program in Data Analytics and Business Computing, including course listings and descriptions, and links to other pages on the NYU Stern Shanghai website, including more information about this and other degree programs.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing, October 2020-June 2021
    Overview of the Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing program taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing Curriculum, October 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Quantitative Finance, October 2020-ongoing
    Overview of the Master of Science in Quantitative Finance program taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2020-2021, November 2020-March 2021
    PDF of the NYU Shanghai undergraduate bulletin for 2020-2021.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Marketing and Retail Science Curriculum, October 2021-ongoing
    Overview of the Master of Science in Marketing and Retail Science program taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Organization Management & Strategy Curriculum, October 2021-ongoing
    Overview of the Master of Science in Organization Management and Strategy program taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2021-2022, November 2021-ongoing
    PDF of the NYU Shanghai undergraduate bulletin for 2021-2022.
  - NYU Shanghai Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The NYU Shanghai bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their graduate program partnerships with other NYU schools.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The NYU Shanghai bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each major and minor, as well as the required core curriculum.
- Rory Meyers College of Nursing (RG 52), May 2014-ongoing
  The College of Nursing (NYUCN) offers a Bachelor of Science Degree with the major in Nursing; Master of Science and Post-Master's Advanced Certificate Programs; a Doctor of Philosophy in Research Theory and Development and a Doctor of Nursing Practice degree.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin, April 2014-August 2018
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Programs, May 2014-October 2020
    Website contains the academic program for the Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Programs. It contains the academic programs from the baccalaureate, master's, advanced certificates, and non-degree programs, focusing on curricula, eligibility, class schedules, academic calendars, academic bulletins, and how to apply to the programs.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin, October 2019
    PDF of the Meyers College of Nursing academic bulletin for 2016-2017. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin Spring 2021, March 2021
    PDF of the spring 2021 College of Nursing bulletin. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The College of Nursing bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their masters, certificate, and doctoral programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The College of Nursing bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate degree programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program and track.
- College of Global Public Health (RG 53), October 2016-ongoing
  - College of Global Public Health Academic Programs, October 2016
    Homepage for the academic program at the College of Global Public Health. Includes information on the undergraduate program, the master's program, the doctoral program, the advanced certificate, and the master of arts is bioethics.
  - College of Global Public Health Undergraduate Courses, October 2016-April 2017
    This page describes the undergraduate courses offered for Global Public Health majors. It contains core course descriptions and syllabi, electives, study away global public health course descriptions, and 2016-2017 course schedules.
  - College of Global Public Health Cross-Continental MPH, October 2016-April 2017
    Degree requirements of core and concentration courses for the Cross-Continental Master in Public Health.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health, October 2016-May 2017
    Course schedules for the Master in Public Health as well as concentration degree requirements and sequences.
  - College of Global Public Health MA in Bioethics, October 2016-June 2017
    Webpage containing course descriptions of the core degree requirements for the MA in Bioethics, course sequences, and course schedules for Fall 2016, Spring 2017, and Fall 2017.
  - College of Global Public Health Applied Global Public Health Certificate, April 2017
    Course descriptions for the four courses included in the Applied Global Public Health Certificate.
  - College of Global Public Health Advanced Certificate in Public Health, April 2017
    Listing of the five courses to complete the advanced certificate in public health program.
  - College of Global Public Health Social and Behavioral Sciences Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the Social and Behavioral Sciences concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Environmental Public Health Sciences Concentration, May-July 2017